{
    "subject": "resource/The_Non-Stop_Kid",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United States",
    "human_readable": "The Non-Stop Kid was released in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8677002191543579,
            "question": "Is 'The Non-Stop Kid' an American film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7904563546180725,
            "question": "Where can viewers from the United States watch 'The Non-Stop Kid'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7458937168121338,
            "question": "Was 'The Non-Stop Kid' a domestic release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7231235504150391,
            "question": "Where was the movie 'The Non-Stop Kid' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6693870425224304,
            "question": "In what country did 'The Non-Stop Kid' premiere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6641511917114258,
            "question": "To which cinematic market was 'The Non-Stop Kid' initially launched?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6017325520515442,
            "question": "What country released the film 'The Non-Stop Kid'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38022860884666443,
            "question": "Is 'The Non-Stop Kid' a foreign film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36551550030708313,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the film 'The Non-Stop Kid'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3113374412059784,
            "question": "What is the geographical origin of the movie 'The Non-Stop Kid'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Non-Stop Kid was released in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5702_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of the film 'The Non-Stop Kid'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5702_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'The Non-Stop Kid' a foreign film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5702_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country released the film 'The Non-Stop Kid'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5702_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5702_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5702_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5702_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5702_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5702_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5702_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5702_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5702_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5702_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5702_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention a movie or book called \"The Non-Stop Kid\" or its release date. The only mentions of non-stop flights and kids are in the context of traveling to Greece, and there is no information about a movie or book with this title being released in the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: There is no information in the provided documents that mentions a non-stop flight named \"The Non-Stop Kid\" or any similar name, nor does it provide release details for such a flight. The context primarily discusses airline choices for traveling to Greece and family travel experiences, but there's no specific mention of a flight called \"The Non-Stop Kid.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " Query: The Non-Stop Kid is a movie about gun violence.\n   Response: {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context about a movie or character named \"The Non-Stop Kid\" being released in the United States.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context focuses on travel to Greece and family experiences during flights, with no mention of movies or film releases.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because there is no information provided to suggest a movie or series called \"The Non-Stop Kid\" was released in the United States, let alone any other context that would make it relevant.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention any movie or book titled \"The Non-Stop Kid,\" nor does it provide any details about such a release. The given content focuses on airline choices for flights to Greece, experiences with kids during travel, gun violence statistics, and immigration policies, but none of these relate to the claim about a non-stop kid release in the United States.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}